<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TORRANCE | WRITING</title>
    <link>/Torrance-Writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TORRANCE | WRITING</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/Torrance-Writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A test post?</title>
      <link>/Torrance-Writing/2019/01/26/a-text-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Torrance-Writing/2019/01/26/a-text-post/</guid>
      <description>library(tidyverse)## -- Attaching packages -------------------------------- tidyverse 1.2.1 --## v ggplot2 3.2.1 v purrr 0.3.2 ## v tibble 2.1.1 v dplyr 0.8.0.1## v tidyr 0.8.3 v stringr 1.3.0 ## v readr 1.1.1 v forcats 0.3.0## -- Conflicts ----------------------------------- tidyverse_conflicts() --## x dplyr::filter() masks stats::filter()## x dplyr::lag() masks stats::lag()Df &amp;lt;- ToothGrowthA page for my Blogdown siteBelow you’ll find a plot of something. inline code looks like this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/Torrance-Writing/2019/01/26/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Torrance-Writing/2019/01/26/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of time preparing blogs in my head over the last six months or so. I am lucky enough to be involved in several different projects, with lots of excellent people. Quite a bit of what we do hasn&amp;rsquo;t and probably won&amp;rsquo;t make it into journal papers. Underneath the smooth (we like to think) surface of our papers there is nearly always technical, difficult, challenging, time consuming, and sometimes frantic, paddling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/Torrance-Writing/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Torrance-Writing/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Mark Torrance. My research explores the cognitive and educational psychology of text production: How our minds turn ideas into text - letters, words, sentences, blog posts - on the screen or page, and how best to teach children to do this well. Quite a bit of my time is taken up with developing methods for capturing writing processes as they unfold in real time.
I belong to the Psychology Department at Nottingham Trent University, but am borrowed - to considerable personal benefit - by the Norwegian National Reading Centre at University of Stavanger and by Raquel Fidalgo, and co-researchers at University of León.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>